eguiders.com 2011-06-01

# Privacy Policy - eGuiders. We Search. You Watch.

### Information Collection and Use

eGuiders, LLC, a California limited liability company (the “Company,” “we” or “us”), respects the privacy concerns of persons that simply browse www.eguiders.com (the “Website”) and each person that uploads and/or views content thereon (a “User” or “you”). Company has created this Privacy Policy to explain the type of information gathered from its Users’ use of the Website and its services, and how such information may be used. Company does not knowingly collect any “Personally Identifiable Information” (as defined below) from children under the age of 14 years.

As a general policy, no “Personally Identifiable Information” is automatically collected from a User’s visit to the Website. However, certain non-personal information, including the type of browser being used, its operating system and the User’s IP address, may be recorded by the standard operation of the Website’s internet servers. This information can be used to help diagnose server problems, administer the Website and generally enhance the User’s online experience. This information will not be made accessible to any person or entity not authorized by or associated with the Company.

Personally Identifiable Information includes: (i) contact data (such as a User’s first and last name, physical street address, city, state, zip code, phone number and email address), (ii) demographic data (such as a User’s zip code, age and gender), and (iii) personal data you submit to Company when using the Services.

When Company collects Personally Identifiable Information from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting such information in use of the Website or because you want us to furnish you with products, services, or information, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to Company for review. This information is used to better service our Users. Any information submitted by a User is provided at his or her sole discretion.

Personally Identifiable Information will not be sold, leased or otherwise made available to any person or entity not authorized by or associated with the Company. However, please be advised that certain Personally Identifiable Information becomes public record upon the posting of such information on the Website.

Certain contact data may be used to determine the demographics of our Users and to distribute statistics and general marketplace information about the Company. This demographic information will always represent aggregate information and is not linked to any personal information that can identify a specific User.

The Company may disclose a User’s Personally Identifiable Information in special cases when the Company has reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with the Company’s rights or property, another User or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities, or when the Company receives a subpoena compelling such information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a User's hard drive that contains information about the User and that is used for record keeping purposes. Cookies enable the Company to track and target the interests of a User to enhance his or her experience on the Website. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any Personally Identifiable Information of the User. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies; however, a User can reset his or her web browser to reject all cookies. If a User rejects the cookie, he or she may still use the Website, although the User's access to and use of some areas of the Website may be limited.

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. As discussed above, this information is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information that can identify any individual User.

If applicable, we use an outside credit card processing company to bill Users for goods and services the Users purchase from Company. These companies do not retain, share, store or use Personally Identifiable Information for any secondary purposes.

### Links

Company is deeply committed to a User’s right to privacy. However, please note that this Website’s Privacy Policy only applies to the Website and not to any other websites that a User may access from the Website, each of which may have privacy polices that are materially different from this Privacy Policy. We encourage each User to be aware when he or she leaves the Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every other website.

### Security

The Company uses industry-standard measures to protect the Personally Identifiable Information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, you should know that no company, including Company, can fully eliminate security or other risks associated with the possession of Personally Identifiable Information.

The Company will not release any confidential User information without the prior written consent of the User unless compelled or required by a valid legal mechanism such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, or when we deem it necessary, in our sole discretion, to protect our rights and the safety of others.

Notwithstanding the forgoing, we will have no liability to a User or to any third party arising out of any loss, misuse, destruction, or alteration of a User’s information.

### Opting Out

Company provides Users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us regarding products and services which you may be interested. You can opt-out of receiving such information by sending an email to Company at info@eguiders.com indicating that you no longer wish to receive such communications.

Notice for Users Outside of the United States

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations. Because Company is intended specifically for Users in the United States, we have written our Privacy Policy to satisfy United States’ regulations and make no representations or warranties regarding the laws and regulations of other jurisdictions. By using the Website or the Services you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy.

Notification of Changes

If the Company decides to change its Privacy Policy, the Company will post those changes on the Website so that the Users are always aware of what information the Company collects, how such information is used and under what circumstances, if any, such information is disclosed. If at any point the Company decides to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, the Company will notify the Users by way of email (if such email address is made available to Company by such User). Each User will have a choice whether or not we use his or her information in this different manner.

### Contact Us

If a User has any questions about this Privacy Policy, the Company, the practices of the Website or the User’s dealings with the Website, please contact us at: info@eguiders.com.

Information that a User provides via general email inquiries to the Company is used only to respond to the User’s inquiries in the ordinary course of business, and is never shared with third parties.

### User’s Acceptance of These Terms

By using the Website, the User signifies his or her acceptance of all terms set forth in the Company’s Privacy Policy. Further, by allowing any child under the age of 18 to browse and/or use this Website or its Services, you, individually and on behalf of such minor, agree to be bound by the terms set forth in the Company’s Privacy Policy. If the User does not agree to accept all or any portion of such terms, then the User is respectfully asked not to use the Website. The Company reserves the right to modify, alter or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time, so Users are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy from time to time. A User’s continued use of the Website following the posting of such modifications, alterations or updates will signify the User’s acceptance thereof.
